Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1983-1993, I.; Cassette 1-390
  - Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007 Mantra (1970). Part 1, 1984-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 106 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 2, Audiocassette 063 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 029, April 14, 1984, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 46:57
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, Michael McCandless, piano; Ole Orsted, electronics
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_063aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_063asc.mp3
  - Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007 Mantra (1970). Part 2, 1984-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 106 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 2, Audiocassette 063 Side a)
    Duration: 20:19
    U.S. premiere; Side b not labeled but is recorded
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_063bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_063bsc.mp3
  - Boone, Charles Weft, 1984-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 107 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 064 Side a)
    Duration: 15:00
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_064aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_064asc.mp3
  - Austin, Larry Life pulse music, 1984-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 108 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 064 Side b)
    Duration: 31:23
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_064bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_064bsc.mp3
  - Ortiz, William Llego la banda (1984), 1985-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 109 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 065 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 030, April 13, 1985, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 11:42
    Performers: UB Symphony Band, Frank J. Cippolla, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_065aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_065asc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Einstein on the beach. Knee play no. 2, 1985-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 110 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 065 Side b)
    Duration: 12:24
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_065bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_065bsc.mp3
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Fox trots again (1984), 1985-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 112 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 066 Side a)
    Duration: 05:05
    Performers: Michael Colquhoun, flute/piccolo; Andrew Stiller, alto saxophone; Rohn Vogan, trumpet; Diana Betts, trombone; Marc Wooldridge, Gary Rutkowski, percussion; Robert Black, contrabass; Michael McCandless, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_066aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_066asc.mp3
  - Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990 Touches (1980), 1985-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 111 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 066 Side b)
    Duration: 09:37
    Performers: Stephen Manes, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_066bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_066bsc.mp3
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Wayang II (1981), 1985-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 113 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 067 Side a)
    Duration: 06:48
    Performers: Michael Colquhoun, flute; Curt Steinzor, bass clarinet; Diana Betts, trombone; Kirk Brundage, Michael Femiano, John Bacon, Jr., percussion; Alan Kryszak, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Gregory Piontek, violoncello; Robert Black, contrabass.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_067aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_067asc.mp3
  - Adams, John, 1947- Grand pianola music (1982), 1985-04-13, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 114 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 2, Audiocassette 068 Side a)
    Duration: 36:12
    Performers: Kathryn Ambuske, Lois Stipp, Rose Marie Gatzek, sopranos; Rick McGirr, Michael McCandless, piano; Festival Players, Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_068aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_068asc.mp3
  - Celli, Joseph Snare drum for Camus (1982), 1985-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 115 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 069 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 031, April 14, 1985, 2:00 p.m.
    Duration: 17:35
    Performers: Joseph Celli, Jan Williams, Brad Amidon, Nicholas Dickman, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_069aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_069asc.mp3
  - Moss, David, 1949- Drums, percussion, voice, small electronics..., 1985-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 116 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 069 Side b)
    Duration: 20:57
    Performers: David Moss, instrumentalist
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_069bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_069bsc.mp3
  - Group Improvisation, 1985-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 117 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 2, Audiocassette 070 Side a)
    Duration: 10:29
    Performers: Joseph Celli, oboe; Malcolm Goldstein, violin; David Moss, percussion
    Not scheduled on program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_070aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_070asc.mp3
  - Goldstein, Malcolm, 1936- Seasons: Vermont/winter and spring (1982), 1985-04-14, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 118 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 2, Audiocassette 070 Side b)
    Performers: Kilissa McGoldrick, flute; Joseph Celli, oboe; Greg Barrett, clarinet; Alan Kryszak, electric guitar; David Moss, Jan Williams, percussion; Malcolm Goldstein, violin; Robert Roush, viola; Robert Black, contrabass.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_070bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_070bsc.mp3
  - Wuorinen, Charles Spinoff (1982), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 119 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 071 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 033, April 15, 1985, 12:15 p.m.
    Duration: 08:13
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Jan Williams, percussion; Robert Black, contrabass
    Repeat performance on Tape 73b
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_071aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_071asc.mp3
  - Horwood, Michael S. Microduet no. 8 (1983), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 120 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 071 Side b)
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Jan Williams, percussion
    Repeat performance on Tape 74a
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_071bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_071bsc.mp3
  - Mais, Chester L. Gossamer piece (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 124 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 072 Side a)
    Duration: 07:11
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Robert Black, contrabass; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_072aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_072asc.mp3
  - Grant, Joyce, 1937- Reflections (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 121 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 072 Side b)
    Duration: 05:27
    Performers: Lois Stipp, voice; Jan Williams, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Robert Black, contrabass.
    World premiere; repeat performance on Tape 74b
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_072bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_072bsc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Knot-holes, bent nails, and a dull saw (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 122 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 073 Side a)
    Duration: 16:09
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Jan Williams, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano.
    World premiere; repeat performance on Tape 75a
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_073aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_073asc.mp3
  - Wuorinen, Charles Spinoff (1982), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 123 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 073 Side b)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 034, April 15, 1985, 1:15 p.m.
    Duration: 08:01
    World premiere; repeat performance on Tape 75b
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_073bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_073bsc.mp3
  - Horwood, Michael S. Microduet no. 8 (1983), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 125 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 074 Side a)
    Duration: 03:08
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_074aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_074asc.mp3
  - Mais, Chester L. Gossamer piece (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 126 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 074 Side b)
    Duration: 07:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_074bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_074bsc.mp3
  - Grant, Joyce, 1937- Reflections (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 127 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 075 Side a)
    Duration: 05:16
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_075aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_075asc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Knot-holes, bent nails, and a dull saw (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 128 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 075 Side b)
    Duration: 16:24
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_075bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_075bsc.mp3
  - Nørgård, Per, 1932- Spell (1973), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 129 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 076 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 035, April 15, 1985, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 17:02
    Performers: Danish Trio: Jens Schou, clarinet; Rosalind Bevan, piano; Svend Winslow, violoncello
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_076aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_076asc.mp3
  - Edlund, Mikael, 1950- Trio (1982), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 130 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 076 Side b)
    Duration: 08:29
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_076bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_076bsc.mp3
  - Ruders, Poul, 1949- Tattoo for three (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 131 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 077 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_077aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_077asc.mp3
  - Birtwistle, Harrison Verses for clarinet and piano (1966), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 132 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 077 Side b)
    Duration: 06:01
    Performers: Jens Schou, clarinet; Rosalind Bevan, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_077bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_077bsc.mp3
  - Lutosławski, Witold, 1913-1994 Grave for cello and piano (1981), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 133 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 078 Side a)
    Duration: 06:40
    Performers: Svend Winslow, violoncello; Rosalind Bevan, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_078aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_078asc.mp3
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001 Charisma for clarinet and cello (1971), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 134 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 078 Side b)
    Duration: 05:36
    Performers: Jens Schou, clarinet; Svend Winslow, violoncello
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_078bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_078bsc.mp3
  - Górecki, Henryk Mikolaj, 1933-2010 Recitative I ariosa (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 135 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 079 Side a)
    Duration: 19:09
    U.S. premiere; Side b is blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_079aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_079asc.mp3
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997 Trio (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 136 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 080 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 036, April 15, 1985, 11:00 p.m.
    Duration: 02:44
    Studio Arena Theater (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_080aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_080asc.mp3
  - Nordheim, Arne Clamavi, 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 137 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 080 Side b)
    Duration: 13:28
    Performers: Svend Winslow, violoncello
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_080bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_080bsc.mp3
  - Ives, Charles, 1874-1954 Selected songs, 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 138 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 081 Side a)
    Duration: 05:04
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_081aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_081asc.mp3
  - Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003 Lied, 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 139 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 081 Side b)
    Duration: 04:21
    Performers: Jens Schou, clarinet
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_081bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_081bsc.mp3
  - Ware, Peter, 1951- Night rainbow (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 140 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 082 Side a)
    Duration: 08:25
    Performers: Peter Smith, clarinet; Robert Roush, viola; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_082aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_082asc.mp3
  - Blomdahl, Karl-Birger, 1916-1968 Dance suite no. 2, 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 141 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 082 Side b)
    Duration: 09:12
    Performers: Jens Schou, clarinet; Jan Williams, percussion; Svend Winslow, violoncello
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_082bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_082bsc.mp3
  - Adams, John, 1947- China gates (1984), 1985-04-15, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 142 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 083 Side a)
    Duration: 05:42
    Side B is presumably blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_083aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_083asc.mp3
  - Reich, Steve, 1936- Music for mallet instruments, voices, and organ(1973), 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 143 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 084 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 037, April 16, 1985, 8:15 p.m.
    Duration: 22:29
    Performers: UB Percussion Ensemble, Michael McCandless, conductor/ organ; Paula McGirr, Lois Stipp, Kathryn Ambuske, soprano; Stephen Bradley, sound technician
    Holy Trinity Lutheran Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_084aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_084asc.mp3
  - Bright, Colin Red earth (1985), 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 144 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 084 Side b)
    Duration: 09:29
    Performers: Mixed ensemble of woodwinds, strings, piano, and percussion, including Brad Amidon, percussion; Michael McCandless, piano; Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_084bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_084bsc.mp3
  - Biscardi, Chester Concerto, piano (1984), 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 145 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 085 Side a)
    Duration: 22:32
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; University Philharmonia, Alan Heatherington, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_085aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_085asc.mp3
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Concerto, organ (1973), 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 146 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 085 Side b)
    Duration: 27:21
    Performers: James Bigham, organ; UB Percussion Ensemble, Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_085bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_085bsc.mp3
  - Jenkins, Leroy Mixed quintet, 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 147 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 086 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 038, April 16, 1985, 11:00 p.m.
    Duration: 13:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_086aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_086asc.mp3
  - Bright, Colin Piece for didjeridoo and bass, 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 148 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 086 Side b)
    Duration: 10:25
    Performers: Colin Bright, didjeridoo; Robert Black, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_086bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_086bsc.mp3
  - Curtis-Smith, C. (Curtis), 1941-2014 Music for handbells, 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 149 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 087 Side a)
    Duration: 10:11
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_087aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_087asc.mp3
  - Jenkins, Leroy Solo violin, 1985-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 150 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 087 Side b)
    Duration: 25:51
    Performers: Leroy Jenkins, violin
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_087bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_087bsc.mp3
  - Penner, Bruce Buffalo roam (1985), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 151 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 088 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 039, April 17, 1985, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 16:03
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; UB Percussion Ensemble, Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_088aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_088asc.mp3
  - Russell, Bill, 1905-1992 March suite (1933-36), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 152 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 088 Side b)
    Duration: 06:34
    Performers: UB Percussion Ensemble, Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_088bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_088bsc.mp3
  - Russell, Bill, 1905-1992 Three Cuban dances (1934), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 153 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089 Side a)
    Duration: 04:02
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_089aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_089asc.mp3
  - Russell, Bill, 1905-1992 Prelude, chorale / Fugue (1984, 1933), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 154 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089 Side b)
    Duration: 07:45
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_089bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_089bsc.mp3
  - Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009 Percussion quartet (1984), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 155 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 090 Side a)
    Duration: 17:11
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_090aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_090asc.mp3
  - Bergamo, John Interactions (1961), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 156 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 091 Side a)
    Duration: 08:56
    Performers: UB Percussion Ensemble, John J. Bergamo, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_091aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_091asc.mp3
  - Bergamo, John Shradhanjali (1980), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 157 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 091 Side b)
    Performers: John J. Bergamo, percussion soloist; UB Percussion Ensemble
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_091bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_091bsc.mp3
  - Shepherd, Stuart, 1947- Birthday music (a work in progress), 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 158 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 092 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 040, April 17, 1985, 11:00 p.m.
    Duration: 16:14
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_092aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_092asc.mp3
  - Csapó, Gyula Handshake after shot, 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 159 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 092 Side b)
    Duration: 03:59
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_092bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_092bsc.mp3
  - Csapó, Gyula Bulgarian kaval music, 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 160 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 093 Side a)
    Duration: 05:40
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_093aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_093asc.mp3
  - Kryszak, Alan, 1961- Coral promises, 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 161 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 093 Side b)
    Duration: 15:31
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_093bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_093bsc.mp3
  - Shepherd, Stuart, 1947- Buffalo chips, 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 162 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 094 Side a)
    Duration: 04:38
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_094aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_094asc.mp3
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971 Le sacre transcription, clarinet alone, 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 163 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 094 Side b)
    Duration: 01:31
    Performers: Unnamed member of the Buffalo New Music Ensemble
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_094bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_094bsc.mp3
  - Bergamo, John Foreign objects, 1985-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 164 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 095 Side a)
    Duration: 05:57
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_095aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_095asc.mp3
  - Reich, Steve, 1936- Marimba phase, 1985-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 165 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 096 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 042, April 18, 1985, 11:00 p.m.
    Duration: 16:29
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_096aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_096asc.mp3
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001 Theraps, 1985-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 166 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 096 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_096bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_096bsc.mp3
  - Deak, Jon Readings from Steppenwolf, 1985-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 167 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 097 Side a)
    Duration: 12:52
    Performers: Robert Black, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_097aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_097asc.mp3
  - Sellars, James, 1940-2017 Piece for contrabass and drum machine, 1985-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 168 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 2, Audiocassette 097 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_097bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_097bsc.mp3